moviecli.ps 2015-12-06

# 

PRIVACY POLICY  
The privacy policy below details the measures taken by mclips.tv ("mclips.tv") to protect your privacy in connection with your use of [www.mclips.tv](http://www.mclips.tv/). Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. This privacy policy is incorporated into and is subject to the mclips.tv Terms of Use. If you do not agree to the terms of this privacy policy or the Terms of Use, please do not provide mclips.tv with any information and do not use the site. Your continued use of the site after the privacy policy has been modified will signify your acceptance of the changes for information gathered after the date of the change. 

The Details  
In general, you may visit our Site and access information while not revealing any individual user information other than Technology Related Information (defined below). If you upload content to this Site, the content will be governed by the Terms of Use and any other terms or conditions on the upload pages. The types of individual user information collected in the registration process may include your name, contact information, other personal information volunteered by you. mclips.tv collects certain personal information when you register with mclips.tv, when you visit mclips.tv pages and when you deliver communications or content to the Site. mclips.tv may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business associates or otherwise. Without limitation, information collected, may be used by mclips.tv for internal research purposes, marketing, promotions and public relations, subject only to the terms of our privacy policy. Please note that nowhere on the site do we knowingly collect contact information or financial information from children under the age of 14. Please review this privacy policy periodically as we may update it from time to time. This privacy policy was last revised on September 26, 2010. Each time you visit mclips.tv, use the Services, or provide us with information, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy at that time. You agree that by using the Site you are expressly and affirmatively consenting to our use and disclosure of the information that you provide, and consenting to receive emails, as described below in this privacy policy. mclips.tv will not disclose, transfer, sell or otherwise communicate your personal information to any third party, unless you give mclips.tv permission to do so, except as set forth in this privacy policy. Notwithstanding the foregoing or anything to the contrary, mclips.tv may disclose any information you provide if required to do so by law or pursuant to a request by law enforcement or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with the legal process; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of mclips.tv or third parties; or (3) act in an emergency to protect someone's safety or legal rights ("Mandatory Disclosures"). As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or change our name or form of entity, and, depending upon the transaction, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets; provided, however, we will not sell or transfer personal information except subject to the terms of our privacy policy. For instance, in the event that mclips.tv is acquired by another company, your persona information may be part of the assets transferred to the acquiring party. mclips.tv will notify you before personal information about you becomes subject to a different privacy policy. The collected information may be provided in the aggregate to third parties, including potential business partners and advertisers, but this information is not linked to any personal information before it is disclosed unless mclips.tv has obtained your consent. 

Cookies  
A "cookie" is a small file that we save on your computer's hard drive that contains non-personal information. These cookies help to give you faster access to pages you have already visited. They also allow you to personalize your pages, and optimize your experience at our sites. We also use cookies to help us figure out how many people visit our sites, which of our web pages they visit, and how long they stay there. This information helps us figure out which of our web features are highly successful and which sites might need improvement. You can disable cookies on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but allow you to disable them. Disabling cookies may prevent you from properly using the Services or accessing the site. Session IDs "Session IDs" allow us to identify a particular user across multiple web page requests. This Session ID is maintained within your cookie file, where possible. If cookies are not enabled, or if the user's internet browser program does not support cookies, then mclips.tv will place the Session ID in the requested web page. This allows the end user to avoid having to continually re-enter certain information such as account name and password for every web page request. This Session ID expires whenever the user closes their internet browser. Web Site Tracking, Reporting Many of our web pages also contain special electronic images (called a "single-pixel gif" or "gifs") that allow us to gather only non-personally identifiable traffic statistics and other aggregate information about visitors to our sites. mclips.tv (through itself or third parties) uses this technology to collect and accumulate anonymous data that helps us understand and analyze the experience of people visiting our web sites and, along with other information you provide, customize your future visits and improve our web sites. For example, we capture data on the type of browser used, operating system software (e.g. Windows XP, Windows Vista, or Macintosh), cookie preferences (whether the user has them turned on or off), and search engine keywords (what keywords did a visitor use to get to our site). We also record number of visits, paths taken, and time spent on sites and pages within mclips.tv's web sites. Please keep in mind that none of this information is personally identifiable and that we only distribute this information to internal staff at mclips.tv and to partners that have signed confidentiality agreements with us. Any information that we do share with partners reflects overall web site or Internet usage trends, not individual. We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/). 

IP Address  
Each time you visit the Site, we automatically collect your IP address and the web page from which you came. In order to administer and optimize the Site for you and to diagnose problems with our Site, we use your IP address to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you. 

Banner Ads  
The Services may include the use of ad banner partners for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions, and other marketing messages. These ads may be provided, in some cases, by a third party ad service provider. The ad service provider may place or utilize their own unique cookie on your browser, and may use non-personally identifiable information about your visit to our sites, such as the number of times you have viewed the ad. mclips.tv is not responsible for the collection of these cookies and is not responsible for the actions of the ad service providers. mclips.tv does not sponsor, endorse or guarantee any products or services advertised by third parties on its site. 

Data Security  
mclips.tv endeavors to ensure the commercially reasonable protection of user's personal information. We have implemented security measures to protect personal information collected on our Site against loss, misuse or alteration. However, the Internet is an open system and technology and human operators are not infallible. Accordingly, we cannot and do not guarantee that the individual user information you have transmitted, including personal information, will not be intercepted by others and/or decrypted or accidentally disclosed. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet, and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure. 

Changes to the Privacy Policy  
As a user of the Site, please understand that our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we decide to make any material changes, we will post these changes on the Site. If, at any point, we decide to use personal information in a manner different than what was stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users of this change by email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. mclips.tv will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected unless you agree otherwise. 

Parents of Minors  
compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we are a general audience site and do not intend to collect any personal information from children under 13 years of age, unless we believe such collection to be permitted by law. Our Site targets an audience that is over the age of 18 and some content may not be appropriate for all ages. Parental supervision is recommended. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under 13 and believe that he or she has disclosed personal information to us, please contact us at [info@mclips.tv](mailto:info@mclips.tv). Upon request, the parent or guardian of a child under 13 may review and request the deletion of such child's personal information, as well as refuse to permit the further collection or use of such personal information. If you have any questions or concerns or believe mclips.tv is not abiding by our posted privacy policy, you should contact mclips.tv's privacy manager by email at [info@mclips.tv](mailto:info@mclips.tv).
